Come on ...
Come on buddy we have to move
Ah...
No..
Gotcha
Take
Wait, please
I flew .. not ..
It is less
L.Ih
It is finished
what Tidak..ITak
Oh my goodness
MenakutikuJOke
Oh, hi friend, you must be disappointed once
yourself in this life
No, no, I'm not late, see
time, he said, before noon
Now you telat.IApa? IKau where?
You missed the party
What is it? IOH, I fell in box
Oh, squirrels
We will see
See it dear
That's why this party is damaged
Tidak.IDan next I will
tell me take responsibility
Hi folks, it's not a story
I messed up out there
That's not a story, I hampirtenggelam
Why was the cake you
Sorry, me?
Who else
Well, you know, I'm not sure
you're going to like this, but
Instead of me like
you suggest, this cake
You!
So you want to hear a story?
Do you think it was free cake gluton
Gluton what it is, what it gluton there?
I hear you, get out of here
Already? But you asked cakes
Hmm .. it's good stuff
Who needs a sense, right?
Uh, wait, I almost forgot
I have to do satisfaction survey
customer before I go, okay
So on a scale of 13 stars,
What do you think the show?
forgive this
My fault
Congratulations, huh, it's a boy
Oh no, our families
always natural childbirth
Risk of deformed babies got too big
That would be music, and
filled with beautiful flowers
And two first face will he wily
His mother and father
We could never get that moment
Now, I do not want my face
so that the first baby see
And what are you talking about, he
probably will not remember me
Father
Go
Ladies and gentlemen, what
I'm loving birds
Yes, as far as possible
That quality, I work hard
for that, right time
And he did not even try
We are pleased
under protection
We laugh
We loved
She likes her voice too
Maybe you've never heard
joke, the rest of the birds
I'll tell you why, because
Where else would we go
good joke
It seems there is a problem disiniJKemarahan
I guess I'm not angry, you are angry
Angry
That we are in our garden
and what are you doing
I do not know, but you
will definitely tell me
Oh, God
Mr. red, when you move
house outside our village
You know nothing
try to stop you?
They smile to you on the road
But that does not mean they like you
Hmm..IHei, you know what,
I have a question for you
Did you know that you strap
life is not interesting to anyone
We all see all
jokes on the road, glorious
And I was like an insult
Father
Mr. Red, Because of the severity of the problem
This, I had no choice
You're going to get punished
the maximum authorized by law
Anger management classes
Oh, unplug my life
Hey buddy, what's up?
Oh, I see you parah.ISenang
I hope to say the same
Thank you
come on
No money
Come on
There is good
Gosh what a no control birds
Left right left right, he
Oh right
Good, feel it
This is it
C) h
Seriously? IAku out. the old man
No
Excuse me
beautiful roses
Okay, be careful
WowJEgoku
Hi Red, what was one of your work?
What? Yeah, with birds
He is a legend
Hell
That topikuJlni mine
Fuck you
What?
Do not see Bobby
That's great
He is mulai.IMundur
come on
Oh look at this, it would be terrible
EFD, m; trash
And it
Three races what?
Hello
I Matilda / Ck
bring with you
I'm really sorry on
what he said to me
Hey all
Halo.IHi nona
Hello bird
Hi, someone did not get the memo
So we're standing on the wrong foot
Okay, red you want to share
your story with us?
No, not really
The question on the child's birthday party
How long this class
As long as you berhasil.ISungguh? Okay
Not nice to meet you
And almost met
Okay, I will continue
Dan..llni diaJTentu, I could sit
So wait here until
I tell court
That anger problem
already completed
Oh, my God
Share with red
Regular ticket prices
I am not angry
So the class honesty, honesty set I
One problem I had was the story
else you said the last time
there he is
I'm his friends
Okay maybe not ice cream
Good, we da
And this Teren
Shocked / No
Teran was the pattern
Now start two weeks
then, it's your story
Sometimes we do not upset me
Has been recognized blow
So as you angry at
akulTidak I burst okay
I exploded like a bomb
That game
Goodbye
Excuse me pal
Do / I can not, just
Bomb bomb before explosion
Hey I do not want here, but this
more interesting, please exploded
you can not do kanlYa you can
So should double-check / Good
Time and place, you are crazy yah
You are
Great, glad to talk with you
Today we do anger to movement
The first dance
come on
And of course with that
Sorry, this looks vomiting
You've never done this before? Yes
How about here Bob
Very good
Just remember to breathe
Mother
Nice
I do not know what happened
Then I lost grip I
Hey where are we pergilmaaf
Yes kitalltu kesenanganlOh no disease
Yeah you know I was thinking
Thought, what is it smallpox
I mean do not hang out with you
Oh yes probably the best I had something too
How can I forget, you said
yeah I can not do
I'm busy too, I was
Business in the offer it
You're not good at this, now it is set
That's one that I know
He opens a new
Luxury class reunion
Ok, fine
Looks so / You want to eat?
Oh what a class reunion
How do you offer
Oh no, I lie I
apologize fool you
No
Hey
L.Ih
Oh I feel
Like what
Therefore
L.Ih
This is the legend of a great eagle
Heroes, but nobody
see him in years
Great eagle missing
When will it be back
What do your parents do not say
Your original giant eagle
He did not know it
Yes, even your friends
This is it
bye
Goodbye / Bye
Here he / Hatchimm / Blessed you
Dad for dinner
If the name I Boby, do you
I asked about hobbies
I WowlNama mood Judas did you ask me?
EhmlAku laughed, I cried,
I love, I hate
I do more
Think about it
That's pretty
You will not make me
menangislltu smart symbols
Uh nice how we hear
kamulAku poetry no poetry
Why not? I do the right IKarena
True / And there is a reason
You know I'll do,
and then i guess
I think and realize
This is the time I
I did not do
And we go back / Chuck
You got your hands every time
I poem about hate crimes
ouch
Oh no, a lot of pain there
What?
Did I make you semualAku for all
Too late, now
I see your face
In masalahlAda people
destroy you from hate
What made him so
You're happy, you're orangnyalYa
Your heart right, and people hate it
Who
Yes I deserve it
Billy has passed? That predication
All join all
Oh good / Let me to let me
will say goodbye
Okay, that's fine
You know there's one thing Billy
always hate goodbyes / Hei
Hey what's going on there
you're there
Move
Hey
That dialAyo
Shoot me
What?
Ah again
Sorry about that
That's no identification ter
Father
your father
Let's stop
That he
Slowly
C) h
L.Ih
APB fuck
That house needs 5 years to at bangunlWow
Wow it really love you
create and destroy
Ladies and gentlemen
we have something for you
Raise your hand to the ladder / Oh
Thank you very much
Greetings from the world of me, the world of pork
That pig
I had the pork
There can be believed, can not be believed
This is it
This 100 will kalilohlkita
We come again
My name is Lennon, my friend call me Chuck
Very good-natured
We have no intention of harming you, us
see you land at sea passed
What do you mean there dialTak
place besides here
Yes there is, and we are from there, we call
Oh, God
Island pigs
Who else out there
The first clerk I
Against this seas
And rose / Sorry
You came to destroy the house
we all, or have I just
OhlAda people would get
Please do not be afraid
I and other colleagues who have asked for friendship
No more
I'm in
Oh no
Welcome
Welcome pig
Welcome there
Welcome
And this dialKita special performances
C) h
You're way around and naked
show themselves
Seeing all of the business / Do not worry
Now we welcome our special guest
Okay, thank you
Thank you for your kindness
Give a speech at the king
You share with our simple island
Cut a better
Wow this is for the vacant world
Yes glorious
100 years from now
All will be no friendship
between pigs and birds
Who cares
Let them say
our Light up the night
That he
Hey, there are many more items destroyed
There are more
Even better, your friend pigs
C) h
That he
Hold for a while I guess
No two people alone
That's not all, this is easier again
Say hello to sling Shoi
Wow
WowlBawa things from place to place, there
Oh you bisallni help me, break
You're off you fix my house
That person
This sling slots do all
in three easy steps
ready
Extraordinary
his friends
That's the same fruit
That last / Shut up and fix my house
We do not know him
I would ask willingly
Who
How the red
I?
TidaklYa turn ye, come here
These days your luck
Are you sure you select 100 birds
Come survived having fun
Come on!
Oh do not malulKau hear
it cries for you
Yes
Closer
now apalAyo
ready
Target / All in this
High
Who says birds do not fly
Oh do not
Hey do not worry I'm fine
Just thanks to lapnya
I hope I've been
do it 10 minutes ago
You know looking
What? I'm not, yes you are right I want
Tun99 "
Let's go
Keep calm
Oh, yes
Nice
Damn / Inside
maaflOh
Gym babilOh
Not strange
Ah ha
Who is this strange man
What are you doing, we try
settles not destroy this place
Wow you're in this place
More stuff here
we hide
I say hi
Hey ho
Hey ho!
There are more of them / Hey hoo!
That's right I kembalilYa / Enjoy
party all?
Because when you get lifted,
I beat her to the bone
C) h
And look what I found
There are more than a lot of them
we think, it's weird
HailApa how are you
He says there are two pigs
ride, but he is clearly a lie
Oh and there was a strange
Obviously you know nothing chaotic here
How messed up I do not tahulDi
see / I do not know
Any question?
You're into boat
I need awards
Yes
You point at me
Excuse me / Maybe I can explain
You see I was an easy cousin
See, A, B, C
not what what you see there is no
He will be at risk, until I found
secure world
We show koboilAyo
Each person on the screen
Maybe it was not not supposed
I believe the bird and
pigs should be friends
But we pass the border
which should not be passed
L.Ih
You're embarrassed, not only to you,
but all our communities
I think you're messed up, you say shame the
I see you treat,
face your problem
Clearly much more care
in butuhkanltidak
Do not trouble us again honored guest
My friends we would love to see
cowboy show you
Let's all
YalBaik do not hear
Nancy
pork rose
Yes let pigs
Her photo / Bilang chesee everything
Charlei
Yes
APB fuck
Hey wow that I remove the toothbrush
Good classroom for today
The soft water can
penetration of the mountain and earth
It's my mind today
this, when we are finished?
What the caterpillar says the final word,
world come butterfly
I never understood what you said
Wow it was very similar
Ah...
Gosh / Let shrewd
Oh gosh, I did not leave it
class disbanded
I said joint
That done
That's what I think
Eggs, children, you do not Eram eggs?
Eggs, we hope so
You look awful my dear
That we
Hey
It is very fragile, you do not
should take and not have you
my friends
That's a nice painting
Oh yes duties draw
That was actually the first in the series
Oh I call this konverser
I call this bye bye
very baguslAku suppose you keep
Your nuts for the winter
Well what is going on here?
What you're cruising or live, for if
you cruise there will be many more to come
My house
And you know what you live
why not say that
How do we do not know
you're not a fugitive law
So not welcomed, you do not
asked basic questions
Maybe I quite jelaslltu
Your opinion is not in need
Why do we have to agree,
Why are we not the same problem
Anger is not always in charge
Continue the tour
Excellent Kalianlltu
you inilBodoh
We could use you now
Hey Chuck's red
Oh hey Chuck child you can come
All of this not only helps
Oh hey just a shower
My friend / I said nothing
nothing wrong with this pig
That depends on our thinking
Think of what sebenarnyalAku not know
Hajar was
Let's not wrong for you? ITidak
I say this, if anyone knows what
This swine mean, definitely a great eagle
That's for you
It's a great eagle still alive? IJika
he lives where he lives
On river policy in an ancient tree
That's a fairy tale, how it
High above
It was a long road that mountain and I honestly
Do you know
What's what are you trying bilanglAku
told me I could use your help
I'm sorry I did not hear the ego
you, you can announce it
I need help kamulOh
why did you not say that
lets do it
If there is a great eagle's why we hear
I do not know maybe we exist
Do you know
You know I have an idea,
may call like
It's more like
That's more like it science / I have one
This is the question
It seemed benarlltu more
set, such as magistik
Wow
Create sound great eagle
That in Sisters
There are people who have anger problems
this is wrong
It's killing me
Oh wow it easily is not authentic
Do not let
What are the talk
Honestly it he
Oh wise you've done in the past
I can say it now
That water is not good, I was kissing
Coiling / Nobody here
There are no people here
You're doing what? out of there
Do not spit
Oh well
Exit, ayolJalan
There is you
Severe Event
Severe
Be it as much as policy,
it was like a river
Or are you something that would be said?
I think he saw
kitalApa you think so?
You were passed the first test
You find me
Caution / Hold
Look ahead
great eagle
I see all and not all
What? IJika you know all,
do not know why we
I know very well who you are
You're a lost soul
here looking policy
WowlBisa we have some?
It is not something that is given
That's something in
maintain / Okay goodbye
TidaklKau with whom
Yalltu I will do
So we climbed the mountain we want to know
OK / For any thoughts you
Bajinganflni great people
Welcome to let
It is remarkable to see you
I have a poster kamulKamu
want to protect your eyes
From that spark trophy
How much / I do not know, do not
I counted gratitude
It's very good
Takeout mamacita
Out of kotalApa hell
That's the old-style lost in sanalYa
YaNVow
So he bit so
You know does not mean you do not wise
You're tired of the inflatable balloon
It's no better way
Helium / Yes
Oh do not worry
As in the ocean, it was a face like it
It's good to come
Free feast, it will be the biggest party
From this year / Party
Ayolltu him
Very good / Hey you're in penjaralApa?
Visible baiklitu I
What I can is dekafi / Thanks
Oh it's the last
Hold, look at me
It's back
Yes back
Singing this song at school
Yes
Yes we did, right
That's the second verse you doing
I. , JAyolAkuZfYallaku right
Make
That he
sing
That accuracy, and more
And broke
Wow you know better than I
And again this pig appeared out of nowhere
Make me suspicious
The road to the rope, I do not
believe, do not understand this
This man sat alone
do not leave home
He's in the game, he only takes care of himself
Looks like you
Oh well thank you for your opinion
Halo / Halo eagle / What are you doing?
What do you see? IAku see birds
No / Vomiting
Oh you're disgusting / Oh yes
You help us or not?
I help you / Do not you help
Binoculars woman tualApa it
Wait hold
Oh, God
I am right
I know / Bom Chuck get out of here
AduhlElang great, fly
we are down there now
TidaklAku'm sorry what?
I do not do it again, I retire
Just take care of your own lelahlPergi
It was I prepared for you segalanyalApa
What, you missed something ISiapkan kitalApa
Let's all this crazy stuff, brag, karaoke
I do not see anything
the world bergunalSeluruh
All that we know in bahayalYa indeed
So you go / You know what?
I used to believe you
When I had children I believe
nothing bad happened
Because you are here, now I see
Fate of the world depends on
fools like me
And that fear pack
It's time for you to go
That made me upset you
birds can fly
Hey let's go finish in
sinilDia no hero
So I was a party next Tuesday
Come run faster
Let's go
That's great
It has been stolen
Pigs steal eggs kitalApa
We must go back to the village
Stop merekalOh golly
come on
We must get telornya
There are people riding
Can you? IPenyusup
What he did / Remove rope
Not bisallni him
It's too strong, I could not opponent
Blow it
Come on Bob you can do this
Come on Bob
You orangnyalApa that make you angry
Try something personal level
Oh you're a snake
You just suck and you know it
Hey
I'm sorry red, I can not do
It's not finished
Courtesy
Who is ready for Allan
Oh no
We'll find them
They are all gone
It is okay
Sir
What are we doing now?
Hold you ask me?
You're trying to say, but we did not hear
I did not hear
We need a leader / A
we do now?
Wait a minute I'm not a leader / OK
Make all you like
stupid, you know what we do
We started changing the children's
Everything is ready ready
We will lay the egg / Stop not
We will not replace the child
We'll get back / How
we will do it?
What does it mean? already show how
That's where they go, so
it's where we're going
But how are we to sanalAku not
Well you know
We will wake up our own boat
They steal your children
They stole our children, intent
I, who did it
Did you steal any child
Did you ever? you like you're going
You know what, I'm a little angry
I predication angry
And I think no one satunyalAyo
We bird / dinosaur our derivative
We do not have good, right?
uh huh
Who else here angry?
We get our children back,
and I do not need quiet
Birds happy, there will be
help us, do not need
I needed a angry bird
You know who gets upset
Let's go
everything
each was
I will not let this
Chuck I need it / Ready
SinilAyo assist in moving all
It's just birds
Hey
Spot telornya!
Wow what in say / Good
SekaranglU h u h
Who thought that?
Follow me
Am I the father, the father
I'm weird
I inilOh rajalAyo
Have been found, I sembahkan on you
Egg
Not rush rush
These two alone
Come Buai
I was a little nervous at
Inside, it is normal kanlYa
I think so
There are other pieces of butterfly in perutlYa
That he
Drop it and the road now
Hold briefly
That the king
He is no egg in the castle
What itulitu where we
pergilhei his friends
You remember everything you've
classroom akulYa
No / Class apalLupakan it now
Now the time off
Oh good Because I did not learn anything
Socialization / I came to snacks
You were not any yah
How can we pass that wall
I told you how we will fly
Remember that castle
To his castle who wants to go first
AkulAku / Good Matilda
Always face burunglminggir
Your Wings siaplTembaklSiap
It came
How is it, I am teacher
can shoot fireballs
In all oranglkau whom his name? IHarold
I see you're doing
I anehlmari show cunning
This is good
It's remarkable we are in history now
You go / No
What we win / There we still draws
Can we get an ice pack / Who's on top
Wow what can you do?
Yucklbutuh tissue?
Who let the standby berikutlltu
You get out there show them
YalOh God
There is
What?
Hajar
Tembaklltu people
Destroy your neighbors
He was safe / rencanalkita fox will eat
eat the eggs to eat
lunch / What she eats
The eggs
Okay that he
Make yourself earodinamisllni?
Launches
Wow it exploded / aerodynamics
View / Wait
Left kamulKiri I left you
We are facing direction samalBenar
We last bird / I could have
Good
Quite far, but not far enough
We should be more closely
I have an idea, you can drag
it was far enough away petapel
For all sanaloke
When to top it
ready
There would be lying to you
You have benarnallstirahat peacefully
Hey fella kawanlSiap firing
Shoot
It would be ill
I hope she is fine
All
There are birds / Bring him on me
Yes Boss
To the castle / Come on fellow friends
That's to eggs
That's the same way
What is it you? IAhlAku
honestly you look a little
Well, you look good, let
Next there pay our friend
With this excessive
We were last there, win, there's
We tried to kill this end
And now we have to
Do you know
Who is next
Hey
Hey wow me in this
Forget
That's not easy
Wow wait endure
Yes it is not authentic
Sorry about that
Take me out
That pain / There is healing
There are no entry or exit eggs
Good I will flee
You too, Chuck I do not know
you could help or not
We think it's way into the room
ldenya
It happened / I'm sorry, you said
C) h
Oh come on
HeilAyo
That he
Everything will be alright
we take it out of here / Road
Stay here
What are you doing up there
My buddy Stable
Do not be so / Back
Oh bung
That's better
Whether it also
Looks just you and me
I take ituNVow
No
we come
Hey / Classical
LepaskanlDi manalAku disbelief
Would do you inilHei
Hey let's wake
That's not a school day / To top two
I have no
Hey how this
I was present, he
Yes
Do not forget that bolalSiapa
Correct
Gotcha
There will be blurred easily
Go
Save yourselves
sendirilAku will save
AyolTidak
All
ApalBerapa many
Photo / Look back
Faster
WowlAku grab it
C) h
You stop yah
There are two answers again
He looked
Not going to happen
Hey
I know what I should do
You're great / I need to stop
Remember me Chuck
Listen / O
That he
Come on Bob you can do this
Beautiful
Hey
You've broken me why the
You / You've damaged my house
Now we're even
Hey
Look out
everything spins
Apalltu everything
Do not
Neither is dynamite
Oh it dialltu try to have me
this tasty
UhlKau can not eat eggs
What are you doing
That finished / You're finished
so this
It dialOh
You know what, I think you win
That plan may
Really? Okay, thank you
That's all I plan
That's a great plan
But you do not plan for this
That I was there for the last time
Yes
You see what I see
This guy is like a statue / Oh eggs
Do not you okay? ISOBAT ku
You see what I'm doing in sanalYa
Oh this egg for you
It's safe
Where dialRed
May be
He hiduplDia life
What
That's something besarlHei pal
Not matilHei / Glad to see you
come on
Pak, bu
I think this belongs to you
Oh Clincy, Woody
You talk about learning kitalKau
Your lesson well
Come on, bring in
uh okay
What's over the limit?
Yes
Fuck / You do not see?
I'll make you lose
trust in me
So did you get strange sendirilltu
Not so rasanyalBilang she Rosie
I do not think it is
happens / Oh look he boasted
I'm not bragging, I'm just red
Nice
Wow is that you in there?
Oh really where they do not exist
It's funny I
Do not forget to cry on
knee I was so, but good
look at that
That tampanlYa / You know it when I'm angry
That really grab
That which is done / I love
go hang out with you
I was at this from the other
look at that
Welcome back
to the village
Ehm / How you
find time this toggles
It we get a pedicure
kanlTidak us there pedicure
You're something else,
honestly I'll miss
But I'm still there is not there
I wake up and see the window you
You can still see the window kamulBenar
So you know
DKE until nantilbh
It's really sensitive anehlltu
Want to eat? ILupakan, let's go home
I kind of sort his friends with you
Sign in here
You bodohllni him
We will perfect butuhllni